http://www.bruceflint.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?Through Google Analytics we anonymously obtain information regarding demographics and interests of visitors to our site. Analyzing the demographics and interests of our users help us to improve our services and online presence to better meet the needs and wants of our visitors. We do not collect any personal information from visitors of our site, except information directly provided by visitors, e.g. for the purpose of registration, making a purchase, signing up for a newsletter, responding to a survey or completing a contact form.How do we protect visitor information?We use Malware Scanning and our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.Third party linksWe do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.How does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Google PoliciesWe use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/501-293-0289?hl=en.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:      • Remarketing with Google AdSense      • Google Display Network Impression Reporting      • Demographics and Interests ReportingWe along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.According to the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA ) we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymouslyOnce this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:      • On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information:      • By emailing usCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#st…Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)We do not specifically market to children under 13.When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify the users via email      • Within 7 business daysCAN-SPAM ActWe collect your email address in order to: respond to communication you submit, confirm an order or send a newsletter.The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can Opt Out using the unsubscribe link or visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ to adjust your browser settings.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
SERVING YOU FROM TWO LOCATIONS
LEAVE A MESSAGE
Since there are three of us and a staff here to help you, leave a message and you'll hear back.
Contact Us
Name:
Email:
Phone:
Describe Your Case:
Thank you for contacting us.We will get back to you as soon as possible.
Oops, there was an error sending your message.Please try again later.
© 2020
All Rights Reserved | Law Offices of Flint, Crawford & Cogburn
Powered by Flypaper
| Privacy Policy
| Disclaimer
The information you obtain at this site is not, nor is it intended to be, legal advice. You should consult an attorney for advice regarding your individual situation. Contacting us does not create an attorney-client relationship.
THE LAW OFFICES OFFLINT, CRAWFORD & COGBURN | TEXARKANA, TX
2821 Richmond RdTexarkana, TX75503-2123
903-417-0588
GET DIRECTIONS
LEAVE A REVIEW
THE LAW OFFICES OFFLINT, CRAWFORD & COGBURN | EL DORADO, AR
201 W 5th StEl Dorado, AR71730
870-862-9400
Share by:
